Nitin Patel

UX/UI Designer Frontend Developer



+91 99243 60366

Surat (Guj)India

🕥 npDesign99

behance.net/npDesign99

npdigihub.github.io/np99

8 Skills

UI/UX Design

App / Web Design

HTML/CSS

Bootstrap

SCSS/LESS

Java/Jquery

React |S

WordPress

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Corel Draw

Graphic Design

8→ Extra-**Skills**

- Graphic Design
- Social Media Post Design
- Print Media Design
- Creating 2D Presentation
- Animated GIFs

Language

English

Hindi

Gujarati



About me

To achieve excellence in whatever I do by hard work and dedication. Desire a position with career growth potential.

Energetic UI/UX Designer & Frontend developer with 6+ years experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive, and responsive websites for IT companies. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. Experienced with HTML5, CSS3, JS, jQuery, React, Bootstrap, scss/less, Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Create suite, Coral Draw, WordPress design. A hard working team player seeking to leverage my skills in the web designer at Microsoft.



Experience

UI/UX Designer & Frontend Dev.

NJ india Group (2022 - Present)

UI/UX, Web & WordPress Designer & Frontend Dev.

AJWebcom Solution (2021 - 2022)

Web, Graphics and WordPress Designer

Contarct Base & Part-time Freelancing (Surat) (2017 - 2021)

Because, Relocated to New City in Surat, Part-Time Worked Freelance in Web Design & Graphic Design, Print design and Video Presentation Design in Surat City. With Contarct Base Remote Job (Rainbowservices - Bharuch Located). And, part-time worked in the family business Stationary Shop.

Web Designer & Frontend Developer

Avanara Pvt. Ltd (US base)(Ahmedabad) (2010 - 2012)

Web Designer & 2D Animator

Vamatoonz Pvt. Ltd (Ahmedabad) (2008 - 2010)

2D Animator & Flash Designer(Contract Base)

Navneet E-learning (Ahmedabad) (2008)



Education

PGDCM (Post Graduate Diploma In Computer Multimedia)

ECIT-ECIL Design School(Ahmedabad) (2007 - 08)

Higher Secondary – GSEB

GSEB-Gujarat(Ahmedabad) (2002 - 2003)

Thank you